《六人行》前情提要…
Previously on Friends
不要过来
Don't come out here.
- 我遇见了理查   - 哪个理查？
- I ran into Richard.     - Which Richard?
我前男友
My ex-boyfriend.
纪念日发生这种事 真是再扫兴不过了
This is the worst thing that could happen.
很好 你最后还是决定 要跟钱德说理查的事了
You decided to tell him about the Richard thing.
糟糕
Oh, no.
- 你不能再跟他见面   - 你不能对我发号施令
- You can't see him.     - You can't tell me what to do.
很有趣 刚才不就是了
That's funny, I think I just did.
- 我找到我的双胞手了   - 什么是双胞手？
- I have found my identical hand twin.     - What's that?
有个人的手跟我一模一样 我要变成百万富翁了
A guy with my identical hands. I'm gonna be a millionaire!
你当真以为我想跟你上床？
You thought I wanted to have sex with you?
才不是呢…
No.
昨晚对你其实也很尴尬
Last night was embarrassing for you too.
我只是没有那么容易尴尬
I just don't embarrass that easily.
- 登记柜台应该在那里   - 啊
- I think the check-in is that way.     - Ah.
你好
Hello.
小孩子最喜欢我了
Ah, kids love me.
嘿 菲比 你们来了
Hey! Hi. You guys are here!
嗨 你去参加化妆舞会了？
Yay! What'd you do? Did you go to a costume party?
我来猜 你是扮庞丘维亚？
Let me guess. Um, Pancho Villa.
你是鲍伯塞吉
And you're Bob Saget.
庞丘维亚？是啊
Pancho Villa?
菲比 你在说什么啊？我不…
What are you talking about, Pheebs? I don't...
天啊 你偷画我？
Oh, my God! You drew on me?
谁叫你弄湿我裤子
Hey, you wet my pants!
这是哪种派对啊？
Whoa, what kind of party was this?
我打从下飞机就是这样子？你实在是太过分了
I've been walking around like this? You have so crossed a line.
瑞秋 等等 男厕在那里
Rach, wait. The men's room is that way.
- 噢   - 怎么了？
- Oh!     - What?
这已经是第三次 那女士接我手玩 结果赢钱了
It's the third time she's won on a machine I was playing.
我赌她一定是那种人
Oh. I bet she's one of those people.
有痣的人？
Mole people?
不是啦 是跟赌人
What? No, a lurker.
跟赌人是什么？
Oh. What's that?
你玩赌博机没有赢钱
When you're playing a machine and it hasn't paid out...
跟赌人等你放弃枕来接手玩 然后…
...a lurker waits for you to give up and then...
杀你灭口？
Kills you?
不是啦 他们半路杀进来 偷走本来你会中的大奖
No, they swoop in and steal your jackpot.
- 噢   - 嗯
- Oh.     - Mm-hm.
- 你怎么会知道这种事？ - 我保姆以前就干这行
- How do you know about this?     - My nana used to do it.
她就是用这收入 帮我付舞蹈… 空手道的学费
That's how she paid for my dance... Karate lessons.
舞蹈空手道？
Dance karate?
对 那是种美丽…
Yes, it's a deadly...
却致命的运动
...but beautiful sport.
- 我弄不掉   - 什么？
- It won't come off.     - What?
什么？我弄不掉
It won't come off.
天啊 瑞秋 你确定吗？
Oh, my God. Rach, are you sure?
不确定 其实我弄掉了 又自己再画回去
I took it off, and then I drew it back on.
嘿…你们到了 乔伊
Hey! You made it!
你朋友是谁？他真辣
Who's your friend? He's hot.
多谢夸奖
Thanks, man.
钱德跟我说过了 电影的事我很遗憾
Listen, I talked to Chandler, and I'm sorry about the movie.
不用抱歉
Don't be sorry.
不要也罢 我找到我的双胞手
I don't need it anymore. I found my identical hand twin.
你的什么？
Your what?
我的双胞手 那个人的手掌跟我完全一样
My identical hand twin. The person whose hands are like mine.
这可是金矿
This is a gold mine.
什么？
What?
靠那个赚不了钱的
That won't make you any money.
好 你这样想也无所谓
Well, fine.
到时我盖了手掌形的大厦 你们谁都休想来住
None of you will live with me in my hand-shaped mansion.
菲比 你例外 大拇指给你住
Except, uh, you. You can live in the thumb.
好吧 加油
All right, baby, come on!
漂亮
Yes! Yes!
- 挡都挡不住   - 摩妮卡 再见
- I am on fire!     - See you later.
等等 钱德 你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
你看呢？我要回家
What's it look like? Going home.
等等 为什么？
Why?
钱德…
Chandler.
你等等
Chandler, wait.
对不起 我只是下来玩一下
Sorry, I was just playing for one second.
我本来打算要跟你说 若你不让我理查再见面
If you don't want me to see Richard again, I won't.
我答应 他对我没有任何意义
He means nothing to me.
得了吧 我又不是瞎子
Oh, come on. I was there.
我知道他是你追求的真爱
I know he's the love of your life.
再也不是了
Not anymore.
真的？
Really?
真的
Really.
好吗？
All right?
忘了什么要回家的事 我们来庆祝周年纪念日
Let's forget about going home and celebrate our anniversary.
袋子里是空的
Okay, this is empty.
我想要搞得很戏剧化 可是我又讨厌打包
I wanted to make a dramatic scene, but I hate packing.
另一个人呢？
Where's the other guy?
哪个人？
Which guy?
高高的 深色头发 手掌跟我一模一样 你看
Tall, dark hair, hand looks exactly like this?
我不知道什么手掌的 不过在我之前的发牌员去上厕所了
I don't know about the hands, but he went to the restroom.
好
Okay.
- 你好吗？ - 我很忙
- How you doing?     - Very busy.
对耶 好吧
Right. Okay.
你好 我有个问题
Yes, hello. I have a question.
我用你们的笔画我朋友的脸
Um, I used your pen to draw on my friend's face.
画了胡子
A beard and a mustache.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不 她不以为然
No, she didn't think so.
我知道 对啊 那其实…
I know. It's like... Anyway...
用化妆品盖不过去 我们试过所有方法都去不掉
Makeup didn't cover it. We've tried everything, and nothing's worked.
这要怎么办？
What do we do?
对 是…
Yeah. Uh-huh.
好…
Yeah. Oh, okay.
多谢
Okay, thank you.
对 这个墨水擦不掉
Yeah, it's not coming off.
什么？那他还说了什么？
What? What else did he say?
他说他觉得我很逗
Um, he said he thought I was funny.
好 你听我说…
Okay, look. Let's just go downstairs...
我们下楼去好好玩 你就会忘记这回事了
...we'll have some fun, and you will forget all about it.
休想 罗斯 我这张脸像这样 绝对不出房门
There's no way I am leaving looking like this!
别这样啦 没有那么难看
Come on, Rach. It's not that bad.
罗斯 我变成人体涂鸦了
Ross, I am a human doodle!
别因为一个白痴在你脸上乱画 而阻碍你玩乐的权利
Just because some idiot drew on your face doesn't mean you can't have fun.
而且又没人会看你
Besides, no one will even look at you.
这里可是赌城 怪人一大堆
This is Vegas. Hello? There are tons of other freaks here.
这里有一大堆怪人 你不算
There are tons of freaks here. No other. No.
走啦 我发誓没人会注意到
Come on. No one will notice. I swear.
是有一些人指指点点
There was some staring and pointing.
我得喝点酒
I need a drink.
冰箱里的酒都太贵了
They really overcharge you for that stuff.
但是谁在乎呢？因为我请客
But who cares, because it's all on me.
你的一点酒还真不少
That is one big drink.
要吃夏威夷果仁吗？
Macadamia nut?
哇哦 这个果仁还真值钱
Um, wow! That's some pricey nut.
你真的很喜欢吃果仁是吧
Really like those macadamia nuts, huh?
不喜欢
Nope.
跟赌人 走开啦
Get out of here, you lurker!
滚啦
Go on, get!
- 嘿 菲比   - 你们和好了
- Hey, Pheebs.     - You made up.
是啊 我没办法一直生他的气
I couldn't be mad at him for too long.
没有钱德的爱 她不能活
She couldn't live without the "Chand love."
啊
Aw.
去开房间啦
Get a room.
- 我们有房间   - 我知道 快去用啊
- We have one.     - I know. Use it.
哦 是啊
Oh, yeah.
可得好好照顾你的手
That's right. Take good care of those babies.
- 你说什么？ - 我是乔伊啊
- Excuse me?     - It's me. Joey.
我认识你吗？
Do I know you?
乔伊啊
Joey?
喔 对
Oh, yeah.
秀手的那个
Yeah, the hand guy.
我们要怎么处理双胞手的事？
So, what are we gonna do about this hand twin thing?
不用处理？
Nothing.
你和我拥有上帝的赐礼
Look, you and I have been given a gift.
我们得要好好利用 好比手部模特或是变魔术
We have to do something with it. Like hand modeling. Or magic.
太空总署一定也想找我们聊聊
And you know NASA's gonna want to talk to us.
- 我得回去…   - 等等…
- I have to get back to work.     - Whoa, whoa, whoa.
我们可以自己组秀
We can have our own show.
我们把手掌合在一起 大家一定超爱看的
We can clap our hands together. People will love it!
哈？
Huh?
我还替我们写了一首主题曲
And I wrote a song for us.
这是你的手
This hand is your hand
这是我的手
This hand is my hand
等等 那是你的手才对
Oh, wait, that's your hand
不对 是我的手才对
No, wait, it's my hand
- 还是算了   - 你还没听到副歌耶
- That's okay.     - But you haven't even heard the chorus!
天啊
Oh, my God.
我现在看起来 好像我姑婆茉莉儿
I look like my great-aunt, Muriel.
你知道什么？
All right, you know what?
其实我们用不着下楼
We don't have to go downstairs.
房间里就可以是赌城
We can bring Vegas up to us.
快
All right, come on.
我们来玩黑杰克 来罗
We'll play some blackjack. Here we go.
- 13点   - 再加
- Thirteen.     - Hit me.
23 爆了
Ooh, 23.
我们这间赌场23点最大
Which is what we play to at this casino!
你赢了10美元
You win $10!
- 我押了20美元   - 没错
- I bet 20.     - Right.
帮我的小钱钱买双新鞋
A new pair of shoes for the Chan-Chan man!
好耶
Yes!
我这辈子还没看过有这么旺的
I've never seen a roll like this!
宝贝 你说对了
That's right, baby!
这次要押几号？
What do I want now?
8号 还是6号？
Eight? Uh, six.
选一个啦 你只有这个任务
Pick a number! That is your only job.
- 8号   - 谢谢
- Eight.     - Thank you.
如果你中了这一把 晚赛就请在场的各位吃牛排
If you get this, we buy everybody a steak dinner.
- 8号   - 好耶
- Eight it is.     - Yes!
我们真的要请他们吃牛排？假的
We're not buying steak dinners, are we?
- 不   - 那就好
- No.     - Okay, good.
- 这次要押几号？ - 再硬押个8
- What do I want now?     - Try a hard eight.
- 什么？ - 4加4啦
- What?     - Two fours.
8号
Eight!
千万要把握住她 你太幸运了
Don't you let her go. You're a lucky guy.
谢谢你 醉赌徒先生
Thank you, Mr. Drunken Gambler.
好 如果你中了这一把 我们就租下这里最大的套房
You get this, and, uh, we get the biggest suite in the place.
我说的我们是我和她
We get the biggest suite in the place.
好 这里最大的套房来罗
The biggest suite in the place!
好耶
Come on!
我爱你 我都忘记我们在吵什么了
I love you! I can't remember why we fought.
因为我和理查吃中饭…
Because I had lunch with Rich...
我也忘了
Me neither!
- 这次要押几号？ - 再硬押次8
- What now?     - Uh, another hard eight.
硬押8？简单8才对
Hard eight? Let's call it easy eight!
好 这样吧 如果这次再中…
I'll tell you what. You roll another hard eight...
我们今晚就在这里结婚
...and we get married here, tonight.
快啊…
Come on
闭嘴
Shut up!
好戏才正要上场
It just got interesting!
你刚才说什么？
What did you say?
你再赢一次8 我们今晚就在这里结婚
You roll another eight, we get married tonight.
- 你是认真的？ - 是啊 我爱你
- You serious?     - Yes. I love you.
我不曾这样爱过一个人我也不曾爱过你
I've never loved anybody as much as I love you.
好 如果再出8就是天意 我们今晚就结婚
So if an eight comes up, we take it as a sign and we do it.
好不好？
What do you say?
- 好   - 好
- Okay.     - Okay.
来吧… 8号…
Hard eight.
有一个是4 另一个呢？
That's a four. And where's the other one?
- 掉到桌子底下了   - 通通不许动
- Under the table.     - Nobody move!
你找那边 我找这边 好
You look that way, I look this way.
在这里…
Here it is, here it is.
一半4 一半5
That could be 4 or 5.
你决定
It's your call.
那是4
It's a four.
我也这样觉得
I think so too.
好吧 又没赢到钱
Oh, well, lost again.
够了 我们去外面解决
That's it. You and me. Outside!
我可不想看到 你美丽的金发少了一撮
I wouldn't want you to lose a chunk of that pretty blond hair!
噢
Oh!
假装没事…
Be cool.
女士 你跟赌的日子结束了
Okay, your lurking days are over.
- 什么？ - 从现在开始 我要抢先你一步
- What?     - Everyone you lurk, I'll lurk first.
不管你找谁下手 我都会捷足先登
You move on, I'll be one step ahead of you...
一次都不放过
...every single time.
我每天都会紧紧跟着你…
And then I'll be on your ass every hour of every day...
直到星期一
...till Monday...
因为我那天要回家
...because that's when I go home.
- 你何时要回家？ - 也是星期一
- When do you leave?     - Also Monday.
几点？说不定能共乘计程车
What time? Maybe we can share a cab.
再加
Hit me.
我们得再去买牌
We need more cards.
对 还要再来点酒 你等等
Yeah, and we also need more, um, drinks. Hold on a second.
喂？赌城吗？
Hello, Vegas?
我们还需要酒
We would like more alcohol.
对了 再来点啤酒
You know what else? We would like some more beers.
喔 我竟然忘了拨号
Oh, I forgot to dial.
一定是送酒来了
That must be our alcohol and beers.
- 嘿   - 是乔伊 我爱乔伊
- Hey.     - It's Joey! I love Joey!
我爱乔伊
Oh, I love Joey!
乔伊跟鸭子住一起
Joey lives with a duck.
你们听我说 我需要帮助
Look, I need some help, okay?
谁去叫我那双胞手合作点
Someone has to convince my hand twin to cooperate.
我去 不管你有什么需要 找我就对了
I'll do it. Whatever you need me to do, I'm your man.
喔…
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
你还好吧？
Are you okay?
对 我很好 谢了
Yeah. Fine. Thanks.
嘿 瑞秋？
Hey, Rach?
你好吗？
How you doing?
宝贝 我很好 你呢？
I'm doing good, baby. How you doing?
罗斯 别再让她喝了
Don't let her drink anymore.
是那颗夏威夷果仁
Here's that macadamia nut.
- 不对 是别的东西   - 糟糕
- No, something else.     - Oops.
好吧 你现在要干嘛？
So, what do you wanna do now?
我要离开这房间
I wanna get out of the room.
我真想念楼下
I really miss downstairs.
我跟你说 要我离开这个房间 只有一个方法
Okay, you know what? There is only one way I am leaving this hotel room.
嗨
Well, hello!
我是罗斯
I'm Ross.
- 祝你好运   - 抱歉 先生 你脸上有东西
- Good luck to you.     - Sir, you've got a little something...
- 你好   - 你好
- Hello.     - Hello.
我赢了 …我终于赢了
I won! I won! I finally won!
是我赢才对 那是我的硬币
I won! That was my quarter!
好啦 还给你 滚吧
Take a hike, toots.
先生 不好意思
Excuse me, sir.
这位小姐用我的硬币玩 这是我赢的钱
This lady played my quarter. This is my money.
小姐 真的是这样吗？
Is that true, miss?
- 卖毒品给小孩   - 什么？
- Sells drugs to kids.     - What?
她卖毒品给小孩
She sells drugs to kids.
那是我的硬币
It was my quarter.
那硬币是她的吗？
Was it her quarter?
我们等吃晚餐再聊如何？
How about we talk about this over dinner?
- 好了 小姐 请你出去   - 不 你不能逮捕我
- Okay, lady, you're out of here.     - No, you can't arrest me!
我才不要重回火坑
I won't go back to that hellhole!
我只是要把你带出去而已
I'm just taking you outside.
那好吧
Oh, okay.
快点 一定要凑齐四样东西 我们才能结婚
I need something old, something new, something borrowed and something blue.
这是蓝色的 而且也是新的
Here's something blue and new.
我们真有效率 我爱你
You are so efficient. I love you.
- 走吧   - 还不行…
- Let's go.     - No, wait!
我们还需要旧的东西
We need something old.
好 我皮夹里有个保险套 我从12岁放到现在
I have a condom in my wallet that I've had since I was 12.
可以用啊
That'll work.
我想应该不能用了
I don't think so.
好 现在只剩借来的东西
Now something borrowed.
- 那就把这毛衣拿走   - 这是偷窃耶
- Here, just take this.     - That's stealing.
到时再还回来就是了 塞进你的洋装里
We'll bring it back. Put it under your dress.
啊
Aw.
好啦 先结婚再怀孕
Okay. One thing at a time.
- 你要玩吗？ - 不要 我没半毛钱
- Are you gonna play?     - No, I don't really have any money.
只是时候未到而已喔
Not yet, anyway.
你不玩就不能坐在这里
Can't sit here if you don't play.
嗨 我是瑞吉娜佛兰姬
Hello. My name is Regina Phalange.
我是生意人 这趟是来出差的
I'm a businesswoman in town on business.
你要我的名片吗？
Would you like to see my card?
我的名片夹到哪儿去了？
What did I do with my Filofax?
一定是忘在B会议室
I must've left it in Conference Room B.
- 14点   - 再加
- Fourteen.     - Hit me.
天啊 我得说两位的手一模一样
Oh, my God. May I just say that you gentlemen have the exact same hands?
一个模子刻出来的
They're identical.
我在商业界做了这么久 从来没看过这种事
I've never seen that in the business world.
别再说了
Stop it.
佛兰姬女士 以局外人的身分 我能请教你一个问题吗？
Miss Phalange, may I ask you a question as an impartial person at this table?
请你别再说了
Please stop it.
你愿不愿意花大钱 去看手掌一模一样的两个人…
Wouldn't you pay good money to see identical hands...
这种娱乐性的演出？
...showcased in some type of an entertainment venue?
只要你愿意离开 我就把手砍下来送你
If you leave now, I will chop off my hand and give it to you!
我不是才把你赶出去了吗？
Didn't I just throw you out?
不 你赶出去的是菲比
No, you threw out Phoebe.
我是瑞吉娜佛兰姬女士
I'm Regina Phalange. Phalange.
小姐 你别闹了
Come on, lady.
请你把他也带走
Please take him too.
我？别这样嘛
Me? Oh, come on, man.
走吧
Come on, buddy.
你不能这样
Don't let him do this. Come on!
我是你的双胞手耶
I'm your hand twin!
嗨 登记结婚
Hello. One marriage, please.
对 我们要结婚
We want to get married.
有婚礼正在进行 先请坐
There's a service in progress. Have a seat.
好吧…
All right.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
那是结婚进行曲 听了有没有吓到？
The "Wedding March." Does that freak you out?
没有 因为那是毕业歌
No, it's the graduation song.
好
Okay.
来吧 我们要结婚了
This is it. We're gonna get married.
你确定你真的想结婚？
You sure you wanna do this?
嗨 罗斯太太
Hello, Mrs. Ross!
嗨 瑞秋先生
Well, hello, Mr. Rachel!
等等 好
Wait. Okay.